邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural
萨姆
Sammy.
赶快带你弟弟离开屋子 快
Take your brother outside as fast as you can. Go!
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad's on a hunting trip.
他好几天没回家了
And he hasn't been home in a few days.
这是爸爸的笔记
This is Dad's book.
我想他想让我们继续他的工作
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔
You know, saving people, hunting things.
家族事业
The family business.
我得找到爸爸
I gotta find Dad.
这是现在我唯一想干的
It's the only thing I can think about.
(开普吉拉多市 密苏里州)
随着气温达到零度以下
With temperatures hitting below zero...
我们已经得到了全县的天气异常的冷锋设置
we've got an unseasonably cold front setting throughout the county.
针对I- 55我们得到大概的结论
We've got some pretty rough going reportedly on I-55...
北风时速40英里…
with winds out of the north at 40 miles an hour...
什么
What the...?
为争夺100亿美元的预算
Republicans are $1 0 billion away from a budget deal...
共和党人像一吨钱一样
fighting over what seems like a ton of money....
《邪恶力量》
好的. - 我想到办法了
Okay. I think I found a way
我们这样从东面绕过这个建筑
We can bypass that construction east of here.
这样 去宾西法尼亚 我们会比我们想象的到得更早些
We might even make Pennsylvania faster than we thought.
是的
Yeah.
问题是 我们不去宾西法尼亚了
The problem is, we're not going to Pennsylvania.
等等 什么？
Wait what?
我刚刚接到一个老朋友的电话
I just got a call from an old friend.
她的父亲昨天被杀了
Her father was killed
她认为这也许是我们所管的事情
Might be our kind of thing.
什么？
What?
是的 相信我
Yeah. Believe me...
她不会给我打电话的 永远不会
she never would've called, never
如果她不需要我们的帮助的话
If she didn't need us.
你去还是不去？
Come on. You coming or what?
你说老朋友 你的意思是
By "old friend, " you mean...?
不是新朋友
A friend that's not new.
是的 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
她的名字叫 凯西吗？
So her name's Cassie, huh?
你从来没提起过她
You never mentioned her.
没有吗？
Didn't I?
没有
No.
我们曾经在一起过
Yeah, we went out.
你是说 你和某人约会
You mean you dated somebody?
而不只是一个晚上？
For more than one night?
你听不懂我说的话吗？
Am l speaking a language you're not getting here?
爸爸和我在俄亥俄的雅典市做工作
Dad and l were working a job in Ohio.
她正在上大学 我们一起出去了几个星期
She was finishing up college. We went out for a couple of weeks.
然后？
And...?
她爸爸的事情很糟
Look, it's terrible about her dad...
但是听起来就像是标准的车祸
but kind of sounds like a standard car accident.
我不认为这是我们应该做的工作
I'm not seeing how it fits with what we do.
顺便问一下 她怎么知道我们是干什么的？
Which, by the way, how does she know what we do?
你告诉了她 你把秘密告诉了她
You told her. You told her, the secret.
我们家族 第一条规矩
Our big family rule number one
做我们该做的事 并且闭口不言
We do what we do and we shut up about it.
这一年半 我一直在对杰西卡撒谎
For a year l do nothing but lie to Jessica.
你和这个女孩出去了几次就
You go out with this chick in Ohio a couple times...
告诉了她所有的事情？
and you tell her everything?
- 迪恩 - 是的 是这样的
- Dean. - Yeah. Looks like.
这是我们这里出版的一份报纸
lt's a newspaper we put out.
不是市长办公室的公告
Not a bulletin for the mayor's office.
把你这些东西拿走 吉米
Get off your soap box, Jimmy.
我需要一些判断力 就这些
I'm urging a little discretion, is all.
不 我想你再告诉我们你想让我们报道什么
No. I think you're telling us what you want us to print...
你想让我们调查什么
and what you want us to sit on.
我知道你很伤心凯西
I know you're upset, Cassie.
我非常喜欢你父亲
I liked your dad a lot...
但是 我想你的悲痛影响了你的判断力
but l think your grief is clouding your judgment.
在同样的一段路上 两个黑人被杀了
Two black people were killed on the road in the same way
就在三周的时间里 同样的手法
In three weeks.
吉米 你和这件事情的联系太紧密了
Jimmy, you're too close to this.
那些人是你的朋友
Those guys were friends of yours.
对你失去的朋友我们非常悲痛
Again, l'm very sorry for your loss.
迪恩
Dean.
嘿 凯西
Hey, Cassie.
这是我的弟弟 萨姆
This is my brother, Sam.
关于你的父亲 我很伤心
I'm sorry about your dad.
是的 我也一样
Yeah. Me too.
我妈妈的情形不是很好
My mother's in pretty bad shape.
我一直和她在一起
I've been staying with her.
我希望她不会被自己吓坏
I wish she wouldn't go off by herself.
她神经紧张 非常容易受到惊吓
She's been so nervous and frightened.
她很担心爸爸的死
She was worried about Dad.
为什么？
Why?
他被吓坏了
He was scared.
他看见了一些东西
He was seeing things.
比如？
Like what?
他说 他发誓他看到一辆很可怕的黑色卡车跟踪他
He said He swore he saw an awful-looking black truck following him.
一辆卡车？谁是司机？
A truck? Who was the driver?
他没提过司机 只是卡车
He didn't talk about a driver. Just the truck.
他说它出现然后消失
He said it would appear and disappear.
在车祸中 爸爸的卡车出现了凹痕
And, in the accident, Dad's truck was dented...
就像被某些大的物体撞击过
like it'd been slammed into by something big.
谢谢
Thanks.
你敢肯定以前没有那个凹痕？
Now, you're sure this dent wasn't there before?
他是卖汽车的 他一直开新车
He sold cars. Always drove a new one.
他的车连刮伤都没有
There wasn't a scratch on that thing.
那天晚上雨下得很大 到处是泥
It had rained hard that night. There was mud everywhere.
只有一辆汽车的痕迹延伸
There was a distinct set of muddy tracks from Dad's car
一直到
Leading right...
他的车翻下公路的地点
to the edge where he went over.
一辆车的汽车留下的泥痕 他自己的车
One set of tracks. His.
第一个被杀的人是你父亲的一个朋友？
The first was a friend of your father's?
最好的朋友克莱顿·索尔姆斯
Best friend. Clayton Soames.
他们一起享有汽车经销权
They owned the car dealership together.
同样的事情 凹痕 没有其它汽车的痕迹
Same thing. Dent. No tracks.
警察说了和父亲死的那天同样的话
And the cops said exactly what they said about Dad
他的车失去了控制
"He lost control of his car."
你能想到你父亲和他的合伙人成为目标的原因吗？
Any reason why your father and his partner might be targets?
不能
No.
你认为那个消失的卡车把他撞下了公路？
This truck ran them off the road?
是你这么说的
When you say it aloud like that....
我对鬼魂的存在与否有一点怀疑
Listen, l'm a little skeptical about this ghost stuff...
这正是你们所作的工作
or whatever it is you guys are into.
怀疑
Skeptical?
如果我记得没错的话 我想你说过我是傻瓜
If I remember, I think you said l was nuts.
那是过去的事了
That was then.
嗯
Hmm.
我知道我没法解释发生的事
I just know l can't explain what happened up there.
所以我打电话给你
So l called you.
妈妈 你去哪了？
Mom. Where have you been? l was....
我不知道你带朋友回来
I had no idea you had invited friends over.
妈妈 这是迪恩大学里的朋友
Mom, this is Dean, a friend of mine from college.
这是他的弟弟萨姆
And his brother, Sam.
我不会打扰你们的
Well, l won't interrupt you.
- 罗宾逊夫人 - 什么？
- Mrs. Robinson. - What?
对于您丈夫的死 我们很伤心
We're sorry for your loss.
如果你不介意的话 我们想跟您谈谈
We'd like to talk to you for a minute, if you don't mind.
现在 我还没准备好谈这些问题
I'm really not up to that just now.
吉米在这个镇上还是有一定影响的
Jimmy meant something to this town.
他是我们最棒的人
He was one of our best.
没有他会大不一样
We won't be the same without him.
我们最棒的人就像苍蝇一样死掉了
Our best seem to be dropping like flies.
克莱顿 我父亲 吉米
Clayton, my father, Jimmy.
你到底想让我做什么？
What is it exactly you want me to do?
封了这条路怎么样？
How about closing this section of road, for starters.
封闭主干路？小镇唯一通往外界的路？
Close the main road, the only road in and out of town?
车祸是有发生 凯西 车祸就是车祸
Accidents do happen, Cassie. That's what they are. Accidents.
警察检查吉米汽车上的凹痕
Did the cops check for additional denting?
看他是不是被撞下去的？
See if it was pushed?
这是谁？
Who's this?
迪恩 和萨姆·温彻斯特家里的朋友
Dean and Sam Winchester. Family friends.
这是我们的市长哈罗·德托德
This is Mayor Harold Todd.
只有一辆汽车的痕迹 只有一个 证明不是谋杀
There's one set of tire tracks. One. Doesn't point to foul play.
市长 警察和镇上的官员
Mayor, the police and town officials
按你的指示办事 如果你不关心
ke their cues from you. lf you're indifferent
不关心
lndifferent?
如果受害者是白人的话 你会封闭公路吗？
Would you close the road if the victims were white?
你是说我是种族主义者 凯西
You suggesting l'm racist, Cassie.
你不该对我这么说
I'm the last person you should talk to like that.
为什么？
And why is that?
为什么不问问你妈妈？
Why don't you ask your mother?
我要为她辩解一下 她很勇敢
I'll say this for her, she's fearless.
嗯
Mm hm.
我敢打赌 他会踢你的屁股的
Bet she kicked your ass a couple times.
有意思的是 你们从没同时看过对方
What's interesting is, you guys never look at each other at the same time.
你看她的时候 她没再看你
You look at her when she's not looking...
她看你的时候 你又再往一边看
she checks you out when you look away.
很有趣的发现
It's just an interesting observation in a.
非常有意思的观察角度
You know observationally interesting way.
你知道我们这里有比这更紧迫的事情吗？
You think we might have more pressing issues here?
如果我触动了你的某条神经
Hey, if l'm hitting a nerve
走吧
Let's go.
打扰了 你是罗恩·斯塔宾斯吗？
Excuse me, are you Ron Stubbins?
吉米·安德森的朋友？
You were friends with Jimmy Anderson?
你是谁？
Who are you?
我们和安德森一起的 保险公司的
Mr. Anderson's insurance company.
到这做一些调查
Here to dot l's and cross it's.
我们在想
We were wondering
死者最近有没有不寻常的经历？
Had the deceased mentioned any unusual experiences?
不寻常 是什么意思？
What do you mean, "unusual"?
视觉上的幻觉
Well, visions, hallucinations.
只是医学上的检查
It's all part of a medical examination kind of thing. Very standard.
- 你说你是哪个公司的？- All tional mutual.
- Hat company you say you're with? - All tional mutual.
告诉我他是不是说过他看见了一辆卡车？
Tell me, did he ever mention seeing a truck?
一辆黑色的大卡车？
A big black truck?
不明白你在说什么？你在说英语吗？
What the hell you talking about? You even speaking English?
一辆看起来很可怕的大卡车
Son, this truck, a big, scary monster-looking thing?
实际上是的 我想是的
Yeah, actually, l think so.
嗯
Hmm.
什么？
What?
我听说过一辆那样的大卡车
l have heard of a truck like that.
你听说过？
You have?
在哪？
Where?
不是在哪 什么时候？
Not where, when.
在六十年代 那时候 有一连串的死亡事件
Back in the '60s, there was a string of deaths.
黑人
Black men.
他们在一辆黑色的 肮脏的大卡车里消失
Story goes, they disappeared in a big, nasty black truck.
他们没抓到凶手吗？
They ever catch the guy who did it?
没有
Never found him.
天哪 不清楚他们到底有没有调查
Hell, not sure they even really looked.
有一段时间
See, there was a time...
这个小镇不是对每个居民都很友好
this town wasn't too friendly to all its citizens.
谢谢
Thank you.
卡车
Truck.
一直在出现 不是吗？
Keeps coming up, doesn't it?
我正在想 你听说过会飞的幽灵船吗？
I was thinking. You heard of the Flying Dutchman?
是的 一艘鬼船 被船长邪恶的鬼魂笼罩着
Yeah, a ghost ship, infused with the captaings spirit.
船就是他的一部分
It was part of him.
那么 我们是不是遇到了同样的事情了呢？
So, what if we're dealing with a phantom truck?
一个被鬼魂附着的卡车幻影 历史重演
The extension of some bastard ghost re-enacting past crimes.
受害者都是黑人
The victims have all been black men.
我想还不止这些
I think it's more than that.
他们好像都和凯西和她的家人有关
They all seem connected to Cassie.
好吧 你负责那个天使
All right. Well, you work that angle.
去和她谈谈
Go talk to her.
好的 我会的
Yeah, I will.
哦 也许你想说一些其他的事
Oh, and, you might also want to mention that other thing.
其他的事？
What other thing?
严肃的没有谈完的话题
The serious unfinished business.
迪恩 你们俩之间发生了什么事？
Dean, what is going on between you two?
我们之间发生的事情比我告诉你的要多
We were a little bit more involved than l said.
哦 好吧
Oh, okay.
也许多得多
Okay, a lot more. Maybe.
我告诉她我是做什么的 我不应该这么做
I told her the secret about what we do and l shouldn't have.
听着 有时候 每个人都需要对某人敞开心扉
Look, man, everybody's gotta open up to someone sometime.
是的 但是我不会的
Yeah, l don't.
和她靠得那么近是很愚蠢的 看这样的结局
It was stupid to get that close. I mean, look how it ended.
你要不要别再
Would you stop?
或者什么的？
Blink or something.
你爱她
You loved her.
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
你曾经爱过她 但是你抛弃了她
You were in love with her, but you dumped her?
哦
Oh, wow.
她甩了你
She dumped you.
上车
Get in the car.
- 迪恩 - 嘿
- Dean. - Hey.
嘿
Hey.
快进来
Come on in.
你很忙？
So you busy or...?
正在写一篇论文 在吉米y那有什么发现吗？
The paper's doing a tribute to Jimmy.
我正在看他的东西 他的奖品
Uh, I was just going through his stuff......his awards.
是着找些线索
Trying to find the words.
一定很困难
That's gotta be tough.
这些年 这个家开办了一份报纸
This family owned the paper. The Dorians?
他们保持着只雇用白人之类的政策
They had a whites-only staff policy.
他们买了报社以后吉米是第一个黑人记者
After they sold it, Jimmy became the first black reporter.
他又当上了编辑
He didn't stop until he became editor.
他教给我很多事情
He taught me everything.
你的弟弟在哪？
Where's your brother?
不在这
Not here.
那么 什么风把你吹来的
All right. So, what brings you here?
我正在寻找三个受害者之间的联系
Trying to find the connection.
顺便问一下 你和你妈妈谈过了吗？
By the way, did you talk to your mom.
关于托德说不是种族主义者
About Todd not being racist?
谈过了
I did.
- 她不想说这件事 - 好吧
- She didn't wanna talk about it. - Right.
刚才 你为什么问我弟弟在哪？
So just then, why'd you ask where my brother was?
没什么 不重要
Nothing. Not important.
也许因为没有他在这
Because without him here...
这就剩下你和我了 而不是你 我 和萨姆
It's you and me, not you, me and Sam...
这样就会轻松一点
Which would be easier?
不 不会的
Not. lt's not easier.
听着
Look, I
不 忘了吧 这样很好
No. Forget it. It's fine.
回到正题
We'll keep it strictly business.
我忘了你会这么做
I forgot you do that.
做什么？
Do what?
无什么时候 我们接近
Whenever we get.
你要说什么？很近？
What's the word, "close"?
要谈到感情问题时 你总是退缩
Anywhere in the neighborhood of emotional vulnerability, you back off.
或者开玩笑
Or make some joke.
或者找办法逃避把我拒之门外
Or find any way to shut the door on me.
这挺好玩
Oh, that's hilarious.
听着 我不是那个关上起决定性的那个大门
I'm not the one who took that door.Wait a minute.
而且 我也不是那个 那个拿了钥匙又埋起来的人
Who took the key and buried it.
我们结束这个比喻了吗？
We done with this metaphor?
我想说的是 当我决心面对问题的时候 你却在逃避
I was totally up-front with you and you nailed me with it.
然后你抓住了这个把柄
The guy l'm with
我不希望这个也许能和我共度一生的男人
The guy I'm hoping might be in my future...
告诉我他是专业驱逐鬼魂的
tells me he pops ghosts.
那不是我使用的字眼
Those aren't the words I used.
他必须离开去和他父亲工作
He has to leave to work with his father.
我必须这么做
l did.
我想的是 如果你想分手 那好吧
If you want out, fine
但是别告诉我这个疯狂的故事
Don't tell me this insane story.
那是事实凯西
It was the truth.
当你认为我能帮忙的时候 听起来没有那么疯狂
It didn't sound insane the minute you thought l could help.
当时 我以为你要甩掉我
I thought you just wanted to dump me.
别忘了 当初谁甩的谁
Whoa, let's not forget who dumped who, okay?
我想你想让我这么做
l thought it's what you wanted.
我不想
Well, it wasn't.
我不想伤害你
I didn't mean to hurt you.
不过 你伤害了我
Well, you did.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
是的 我也是
Yeah, me too.
我们应该多吵架. -
We should fight more often.
绝对
Absolutely.
事实上 我们很擅长吵架
Actually, we were always pretty good at fighting.
是的 我们很擅长
This we were good at.
但是其他的事就不这样
It's all the other stuff, not so much.
嘿 我尽力了
Hey, I tried.
我告诉了你我是谁 那是我很大的进步
told you who l really was. That was a big first for me.
你为什么要告诉我？
Why'd you tell me?
我不知道
I don't know.
我…
I....
我猜我不想对你撒谎
I guess I couldn't lie to you.
迪恩
Dean.
当你告诉我那个故事
You told me that story...
你把我吓坏了
it scared the hell out of me.
我当时以为你是一个傻瓜 还很危险
I thought you were nuts. Dangerous even.
实际上
Actually...
也许我当时在找一个离开的理由
maybe l was looking for a reason to walk away.
在我工作时 我看到过很多恐怖的事
In my work...I see some horrible things.
没法解释的事
Things that can't be explained.
我解决它们
I deal with them.
但是解决我们之间的事
But working things out with you?
我很恐怖 是吗？
l'm a scary one, all right.
嗯
Hmm.
通常 如果你希望事情得到解决
Well, usually things get worked out...
他们就会得到解决
when you really want them to.
但是我非常关心我爸爸的工作
Yeah, but l'm still really involved with my dad's work.
不要再找借口了好吗？你我都不要
more excuses, okay? From you or me.
好吧
Okay.
好
Yeah?
你在开玩笑
You're kidding.
他和我是一起的
He's with me.
你昨晚在哪？
Where were you last night?
你没有回汽车旅馆
You didn't make it back to the motel.
没有
Well....
我想你们有进展了
You guys worked things out?
当我们90岁时 也许会的
We'll be working things out when we're 90.
发生什么事了？
So, what happened?
每块骨头都粉碎了 内脏几乎成了布丁状
Every bone crushed. Internal organs turned to pudding.
警察都被难住了
The cops are stumped.
就像他被某物撞倒了
It's like something ran him over.
比如卡车？
Something like a truck?
是的
Yep.
没有痕迹？
Tracks?
没有
Nope.
市长在干什么？
What was the mayor doing here?
他有了一些财产 前几个星期购买的
He owned the property. Bought it a few weeks ago.
是的 但是他是白人 不符合特征
But he's white, doesn't fit the pattern.
谋杀不是发生在公路上
Killings didn't happen up on the road.
这也不符合
That doesn't fit, either.
给
Here.
谢谢
Thanks.
我正在找六十年代发生的谋杀之间的联系
I'm trying to find some link between the '60s and now.
报纸上没有太多的报道
There wasn't a lot about it in the paper.
并不惊奇 也许是警察的大事化小 小事化了的做法
Not surprising. Probably minimal police work too.
当时 这儿的法律 没有过多的文书记录
Back then, equal justice under the law wasn't too literal around here.
什么？
Yeah?
法院的纪录记载
The records......
市长夫妇购买了一份被遗弃的财产
Show that Mr. Mayor bought an abandoned property.
先前的所有这是多利安一家 有150年了
The previous owner was the Dorian family for, like, 150 years.
多利安？
Dorian?
是的
Yeah.
你不是说过多利安一家是报社的所有者？
Didn't the Dorian family used to own this paper?
这所有的一切
Along with most everything else.
是这个小镇的栋梁
Real pillars of the town.
对 对
Right, right.
很有趣
That's interesting.
什么？
What?
这个赛勒斯·多利安在63年4月失踪了
This Cyrus Dorian.He vanished in April of '63.
他们调查了这个案子 但是没有解决
The case was investigated, but never solved.
那也是一系列谋杀案发生的时候
That's the time the murders were going on.
我在多利安家里找到了一堆报纸
I pulled paper up on the Dorian place. Must've been in bad shape...
当市长买那些财产的时候 当时这个地方一定很糟
when the mayor bought it.
为什么这么说？
Why?
他做的第一件事就是平整了这片土地
The first thing he did was bulldoze.
托德市长拆了那个房子？
Mayor Todd knocked down the place?
那是一桩大买卖 那是小镇遗留下来的最老的房子之一
It was a big deal. One of the oldest local houses left.
成了头版头条
He made the front page.
是在哪天发生的？
You got a date?
上月3号
Uh, the 3rd of last month.
托德市长 3号 拆了多利安的房子
Mayor Todd bulldozed the Dorian family home on the 3rd.
第一起谋杀是在第二天
The first killing was the very next day.
迪恩
Dean. Dean!
也许你可以调查一下
Maybe you could throw a couple shots in that.
你没有看见谁开卡车？
You didn't see who was driving the truck?
看起来没有人
It seemed to be no one.
一切变化得太快
Everything was moving so fast.
然后它就消失了
And then it was just gone.
为什么它没有杀了我们？
Why didn't it kill us?
不管是什么控制着卡车 他想要让你害怕
Whatever's controlling the truck wants you afraid first.
罗宾逊夫人 凯西说你的丈夫看见了卡车
Mrs. Robinson, Cassie said that your husband saw the truck.
在他死之前
Before he died.
妈妈
Mom?
嗯
Mm hm.
马丁当时压力很大
Oh, Martin was under a lot of stress.
你不能肯定他当时看到了什么
You can't be sure about what he was seeing.
今晚以后 我想我们有理由肯定
After tonight, we can be reasonably sure...
他看见的是一辆卡车
that he was seeing a truck.
今晚发生了的事说明 你和凯西被人盯上了
What happened tonight, you and Cassie are marked.
你的女儿会死的 所以如果你知道什么事情
Okay? Your daughter could die. So if you know something...
现在告诉我们 这是非常恰当的时候
now would be a good time to tell.
迪恩…
Dean
什么？
Yes.
是的 他说他看见了卡车
Yes. He said he saw a truck.
他说卡车是谁的了吗？
Did he know who it belonged to?
他认为他知道
He thought he did.
是谁的？
Who was that?
赛勒斯
Cyrus.
那个人叫赛勒斯
A man named Cyrus.
这人是赛勒斯吗？
Is this Cyrus?
赛勒斯·多利安四十多年前就死了
Cyrus Dorian died more than 40 years ago.
你怎么知道他死了 罗宾逊夫人？
How do you know he died, Mrs. Robinson?
报纸上说他失踪了
The paper said he went missing.
你怎么知道他死了？
How do you know he died?
我们当时都很年轻
We were all very young.
我和赛勒斯 约会了一阵子
I dated Cyrus a while.
我当时也偷偷地和马丁在一起
I was also seeing Martin. In secret.
因为不同人种之间的结合结果都不是很好
of course because interracial couples didn't go over too well then.
我和赛勒斯 分手 当他发现马丁的事
When I broke it off with Cyrus and when he found out about Martin...
我不知道… 他变了
l don't know, he changed.
他的愤怒 他的愤怒很令人害怕
s hatred. His hatred was frightening.
关于一系列的谋杀
The string of murders.
有谣言说 黑人失踪在一种能自动驾驶的卡车里
There were rumors. People of color disappearing into some kind of a truck.
关于这件事 人们并没有做什么
Nothing was ever done.
马丁和…
Martin and...
马丁和我
Martin and I
从来都没有想要 在这附近的小教堂里结婚
We were gonna be married in that little church near here.
但是 最后我们决定私奔
But last minute, we decided to elope because
因为我们不想引起注意
We didn't want the attention.
赛勒斯呢？
And Cyrus...?
我们决定的婚期
The day we set for the wedding...
就是教堂起火的那天
Was the day someone set fire to the church.
那有个儿童唱诗班在那儿练习
There was a children's choir practicing in there.
他们都死了
They all died.
袭击事件就此停止了吗？
Did the attacks stop after that?
没有 还有一件
No. There was one more.
一天晚上 卡车来找马丁
One night, that truck came for Martin.
赛勒斯狠狠地打他
Cyrus beat him something terrible.
但是马丁 他解脱出来
But Martin, you see, Martin got loose.
开始打赛勒斯
And he started hitting Cyrus...
他一直不停的打他. -
and he just kept hitting him and hitting him and....
你为什么不叫警察？
Why didn't he call the cops?
那是40年前的事了
This was 40 years ago.
他召来了他的朋友
He called on his friends...
克莱顿和吉米
Clayton Soames and Jimmy Anderson.
他们把赛勒斯的尸体放进了卡车
And they put Cyrus' body into the truck...
然后把车推进了土地边缘的沼泽
and rolled it into the swamp at the edge of his land...
这么多年来 他们守口如瓶
and all three of them kept that secret all these years.
现在他们三个都死了
And now all three are gone.
托德市长也死了
So is Mayor Todd.
他说 你是这么多人中最清楚
Now, he said that you of all people would know
他不是种族主义者
He's not a racist.
为什么他要这么说？
Why would he say that?
他是个好人
He was a good man.
当时他是个年轻的副官
He was a young deputy back then...
调查赛勒斯的失踪案
investigating Cyrus' disappearance.
当他发现马丁和其他的人都干了些什么
Once he figured out what Martin and the others had done...
他什么也没做
He did nothing.
因为他也知道赛勒斯都做了些什么
Because he also knew what Cyrus had done.
为什么你没有告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me?
我觉得我在保护他们
I thought l was protecting them.
现在没有人需要我袒护了
And now there's no one left to protect.
当然有
Yes, there is.
我的生活很简单
Ah, my life was so simple.
只是上学 考试
Just school, exams...
多中心文化规范的论文
papers on polycentric cultural norms.
所以 我猜我把你从无聊的生活中解救出来
I guess I saved you from a boring existence.
偶尔我还会想念无聊的生活
Yeah. Occasionally, l miss boring.
那么 这杀人卡车
So this killer truck....
我真希望对话不是以杀人卡车开头
I miss conversations that didn't start with "this killer truck."
啊…
Ah...
好吧 这个叫赛勒斯的人
All right, so this Cyrus guy. Yeah.
从某种角度讲他很邪恶 甚至影响了他的卡车
Evil on a level that infected even his truck.
当他死了 沼泽成了他的坟墓
When he died, the swamp became his tomb...
他的灵魂隐匿了40年
and his spirit was dormant for 40 years.
那么什么唤醒了他？
So, what woke it up?
他的房子的修建或者损坏
The construction on his house. Or the destruction.
对了
Right.
破坏或者重新改造能唤醒灵魂
Demolition or remodeling can awaken spirits.
让它们不得安宁
Make them restless.Mm hm.
就像伊利诺斯州的歌剧院一样
Like that theater in lllinois?
是的
Yup.
推倒家宅的人
And the guy who tears down the family homestead.
哈罗德·托德就是那个
, Harold Todd is
对赛勒斯的凶杀案保持沉默 并且没有解决那个案子的人
The same guy that kept Cyrus' murder quiet and unsolved.
所以他的灵魂被唤醒 出来进行血腥的谋杀
So now his spirit is awakened and out for blood.
这是我的想法 谁知道鬼魂是怎么想的
I guess. Who knows what ghosts are thinking.
我们要把尸体从沼泽里挖出来
You know we're gonna have to dredge that body up from the swamp.
伙计
Man.
你竟然这么说了
You said it.
是的
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
她睡着了
She's asleep.
现在怎么办？
Now what?
你要保持清醒 看护着她
Well, you stay put and look after her...
我们会回来 别离开房子
and we'll be back. Don't leave the house.
别命令我
Don't go getting all authoritative on me.
我最恨这样
I hate it.
请别离开房子
Don't leave the house, please?
你来不来？
You coming or what?
好 我们现在把它拉上来
All right. Let's get her up.
在上来点儿
All right.
Little more. Little more.
在上来点儿
Little more.
好 停
All right, stop.
很好
Nice.
是啊
Hell, yeah.
现在我知道她看上你什么了
Now l know what she sees in you.
什么？
What?
你可以承认 你还爱着她
Come on, admit it. You're still in love with her.
我们集中精神好吗？
Aw, could we focus, please?
我只是说说迪恩
I'm just saying, Dean.
- 拿着那个 - 好的
- Hold that. - All right.
我拿着什么呢？
What am l getting?
瓦斯手电筒
Gas, flashlight.
拿到了
Got it.
- 我们把它拉上来 - 好
- Let's get this done. - All right.
好吧 我们开始干吧
All right, let's get to it.
这样就行了吗？
Think that'll do it?
我想不行
I guess not.
烧了尸体就对那东西没有影响吗？
So burning the body had no effect?
- 当然有 - 现在它很愤怒
- Sure it did. - Now it's really pissed.
- 但是赛勒斯灵魂已经走了 是吗 迪恩？- 没错
- But Cyrus' ghost is gone. - right?
很显然不是控制着卡车的那部分
Not the part that's fused with the truck.
你去哪？
Where are you going?
- 去兜风 - 什么？- 把那东西带走
- For a little ride. - What? - Lead that thing away.
那个生锈的骰子 你最好烧了它
That piece of crap, burn it.
我怎么烧一个骰子 迪恩？
- How am l supposed to burn it? - l don't know.
我不知道 自己想办法
Figure something out.
想办法
Figure something...?
- 嘿 你得给我点时间 - 我们没有时间了 你在做什么？
- Give me a minute. - l don't have a minute.What are we doing?
一会在和你说
Uh, let me get back to you.
嘿 卡西？嘿 这是萨姆
Hey, Cassie? Hey, it's Sam.
我需要你告诉我一些事情 必须要准确
Okay, l need some information and it has to be exactly right.
- 好吧 迪恩 - 这最好变得顺利点
- All right. - This better be good.
你在哪？
Where are you?
我在半路上 在杀人卡车里
The middle of nowhere with a killer truck on my ass.
它好像知道我烧了赛勒斯的尸体
It knows l put the torch to Cyrus.
迪恩听着 这很重要
Listen. lt's important.
我必须知道你确切的位置
I have to know exactly where you are.
迪凯特大街 离高速公路两英里
Decatur Road, about two miles off the highway.
向东行驶？
Okay. Headed east?
是的
Yes!
狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
向右拐 向右 向右拐
Okay, turn right. Up ahead, turn right.
你转弯了吗？
You make the turn?
是的 我转弯了
I made it.
把那个东西再开快点
Move this thing along a little faster.
你看见前面有一条路？
You see a road up ahead?
没有
No. Wait.
等等 是的 我看见了
Yes. I see it.
好 左转
Okay, turn left.
什么？
What?
好吧 现在怎么办？
All right. Now what?
精确行驶0. -7英里然后停下
Go seven tenths of a mile and stop.
停下
Stop?
精确的 7/10英里
DeanExactly seven-tenths, Dean.
7/10 7/10
Seven-tenths, seven-tenths.
迪恩你还在吗？
Dean, you still there?
是的
Yeah.
发生什么事了？
What's happening?
它正在盯着我 我该怎么做？
It's staring at me. What do I do?
- 做你正在做的事 - 把它引过来
- What you are doing. - Bringing it to you.
什么
Yeah.
加油 加油
Come on. Come on.
你还在吗？Dean？
Dean? You still there?
迪恩？
Dean.
它去哪了？
Where did it go?
迪恩 你正在教堂的位置
Dean, you're where the church was.
什么教堂？
What church?
赛勒斯烧的地方 杀了所有的孩子
The place Cyrus burned down. Murdered those kids.
没有留下什么东西
There's not a lot left.
教堂的土地是神圣的
Church ground is hallowed.
不管教堂是否还在
Whether the church is there or not.
邪恶的灵魂在神圣的土地周围盘旋
Evil spirits cross over hallowed ground.
有时候他们被损坏了
Sometimes they're destroyed.
所以我想那也许能除掉他
So l figured maybe that would get rid of it.
也许
Maybe?
万一你是错的呢？
What if you were wrong? Huh.
说实话 我从来没这么想过
Honestly, that thought hadn't occurred to me.
说实话 我从来没遇到这种事
"Well, it honestly didn't occur to me."
我要杀了他
I'm gonna kill him.
我妈妈说再次谢谢你
My mother says to tell you thanks again.
这比上次的再见要好得多
This is a better goodbye than last time.
也许这次离别 没有那么久
Yeah, well, maybe this time it'll be a little less permanent.
你知道吗？我是个现实主义者
u know what? I'm a realist.
我认为我们之间没有希望 Dean
I don't see much hope for us, Dean.
我见过一些人 他们彼此是陌生人
Well, l've seen stranger things happen.
但是他们最后走到了一起
Hell of a lot stranger.
再见 迪恩
Goodbye, Dean.
我会再见到你的cassie
I'll see you, Cassie.
我会的
I will.
我喜欢她
I like her.
是的
Yeah.
你见到过像她一样的女孩吗？
You meet someone like her.
我一直在想
Ever make you wonder.
我们为了我们的工作付出这么多 值得吗？
If it's worth it putting everything else on hold, doing what we do?
当轮到我开车的时候叫醒我？
Why don't you wake me up when it's my turn to drive?